so I already did a video today this
morning it was requesting a coder to
contact me so we can create this
schedule ena and then I drop my kid off
at school I was supposed to clean my
house to go on this vacation but I've
not cleaned it for the last two days
I've been too busy doing other things
and procrastinating and so I downloaded
tik-tok because I felt the urge to do
that for a while it's where I think I
can find my younger generation who is
ready to change the world and has the
tech skills to do it so I started a
project talking that might not be
because whenever I sign up for something
with that goal in mind
it never is that like putting up the
coding video I posted on my facebook I
posted this women in tech and I posted
in-game B and the two people responded
in game B both gave me app things that
to look at that are doing something
similar not the same thing but something
very similar 29 K which is amazing and I
only just downloaded it was the
incentive to do this video because like
all these things are happening really
weirdly he responded while I was on an
idea cafe with these two amazing women
who are dealing with the Kyle sees
fallout as well as what I'm dealing with
and that we made public on the idea cafe
YouTube we voted to make it public but
had that amazing conversation and
afterwards Kim gave me two two resources
that were exactly what I needed one
around food and one around this coaching
idea which 29k it looks like they also
are the ones doing the work and it's
already up and available it's like
online coaching that as far as I can
tell so far is free it's not for profit
and then I so I downloaded tik-tok to
get close to to figure out the
generation right there on it
they're like the teenagers and 20 year
olds and so I find out my room was the
best and I used it as the incentive to
clean my room that was my first video my
first and only video is messy room me
snapping and then my clean room
it's a horrible video but it gave me the
incentive to clean it and then these
four new resources that I have is also
like we need to get these things
organized the fact I've been out there
looking for a scheduling app and the one
didn't solve the scheduling
more just coordination of video with
people and it could look the similar for
the layout and the other one is I've yet
to get to the video part but it's
basically how we evolve together and be
happy through an app but together like
yep thank you someone made it and so
thinking about how we can coordinate the
organization of just knowing amazing
projects that are out there and how do
we get involved is both what the meta
project is doing and also what I'm
feeling called to kind of move on next
is still concentrating on the four
questions just like not feeling the
overwhelming pressure of needing to save
the world but the gratitude of getting
to do it in an easy fun way that works
for me getting to follow the next step
getting to just live my day and these
amazing things show up I don't know if
I'm gonna find a coder to create the
schedule early not no idea but it wasn't
about that it was about listing posting
it and then finding these other
resources and just thank you thank you
for the for all of the lessons the
universe gives me despite the fact that
I swear at it constantly like seriously
these absolutely exist but we've been
looking for them for how long and like
I'm just now figuring them we need to
get this organized so everyone
doesn't have to go through this process
I am looking for these things that I
can't even find them I can't imagine if
you weren't even looking for them and
how they then find you when you also
don't understand that the universe is
giving you all the tools in the right
time in the right order to be open to
seeing these four resources five I guess
tick-tock was also a resource all right
take care I will see you tomorrow I'm
trying to do only one video today but
today's the two video yet